grocerycouponhub.com 2011-12-01

# Privacy Policy

**** **  
**

GroceryCouponHub.com

Privacy Policy  
****

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEBSITE.  GroceryCouponHub.com (“Company”) and GroceryCouponHub.com (“the Website”) (collectively “we”) are committed to protecting the privacy and security of our users of the Website.  This Privacy Policy sets forth how the Website collects and uses personal information.  By using this Website, you acknowledge that you have read and accepted our privacy practices set forth below.

If you do not accept our privacy practices, then you should not continue to use this Website.  This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference into and forms part of our Terms of Use.

**1\. Confidentiality and Security of Personal Information**

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect personally identifiable information sent to our Website, both during transmission and afterwards.  We maintain our servers in a secure and environmentally controlled location, and we utilize Advanced Policy Firewall to protect our network.  In addition, we do not store users’ information on computers which are not connected to the Internet, and we actively limit employee, agent, and service providers’ access to our users’ information. 

However, despite our efforts to maintain your confidentiality and security, no method of transmission over the Internet and no method of electronic storage is completely secure.  Although we make every effort to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**2\. Personal Information We Will Collect**

We do not require you to create an account to log in to our Website, but we do require you to submit some basic information in order to view the opportunities offered on our website, including but not limited to name and email address. 

We will collect and log the IP address of your computer in order to enable us to detect unauthorized transactions and to better manage website traffic, and to detect and log the name of the website they are navigating.  In addition, we utilize geo-IP technology to capture and log a user’s zip code, city, state, region, and country.  Moreover, we automatically associate collected and logged information with users’ information that they submit. We also may occasionally supplement the information we collect from our Website with information we receive from outside sources. 

We do not collect financial information from our users, nor do we require a user name or password from our registrants.  Similarly, we do not collect information about our users’ buying behavior, nor do we capture information regarding the next website that the user visits after he or she leaves our Website. 

**3.  Purposes for Which We Will Use Personal Information**

We make every effort to identify the purposes for which we will collect personal information at or before the time the information is collected.  We will use your personal information only for the purposes disclosed at the time of collection or as otherwise set out in this Privacy Policy, unless we have your consent for another use, or unless such other use is authorized or required by law.  
Our policy is to collect personal information from you for the following purposes:

> (a) to identify your needs and/or preferences;  
>  (b) to email you certain marketing offers;  
>  (c) to use standard analytics tracking on our Website;  
>  (d) to provide tracking/conversion information about users clicking on advertisements;  
>  (e) to meet legal and regulatory requirements;  
>  (f) to administer, maintain, manage, and improve our business operations; and   
>  (g) as otherwise required by law.

**4\. Sharing of Personal Information**

This Website will only share personal information with third parties under the following circumstances:

> (a) We may share your personal information if required by law and if we believe that the disclosure is required or necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial processing or legal process served on our Website.  
>  (b) We may share personal information if we believe that it is required in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, a potential threat to the physical safety of a third party, or as otherwise required by law.  
>  (c) We may transfer personal information to a third party entity in the event of an assignment of this Website for any reason.  You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of personal information.  
>  (d) We may share your personal information with our legal, financial, and other professional advisors.  
>  (e) We may share your personal information with affiliated third parties to bring you select opportunities via direct mail, email, and telemarketing.   
>  (f) We may share personal information with website developers in the event that we are upgrading or improving our Website.  
>  (g) We may share personal information with third parties upon receiving your consent as required by law.  
>  Except as provided above, we will not share any of your information to any third party without permission.  All companies to whom we share information have or will be provided our current Privacy Policy and shall be required to follow strict compliance regarding CAN-SPAM as well as other email and telemarketing regulations, including appropriate subscriber opt-out procedures.  In addition, we will send each of these companies or third parties every ten (10) days a regular update of our email suppression/removal lists in order to synchronize removed subscribers from the lists. 

**5\. Access to Your Personal Information**  

You can review, update, delete, or correct your personal information on file with us online or by submission of a written request.  To update your personal information, we require a written request (mailed to us at the address listed in the “Contact Us” section below; or to remove your personal information from our database electronically, please refer to the “Contact With You” section below.  Upon receipt of any written request, we will take commercially reasonable steps to provide you with the opportunity to access any such information. 

**6\. Email Requests for Personal Information**

We will never initiate a request for personal information by email.  If you receive a request by email, please do not respond and notify us as set forth below. If you ever believe that you have been a victim of fraud, please report it to the police and take all available actions to protect yourself.  Also, please notify us, so that we can take all possible actions to protect you and the other users of this Website.

**7\. Children**

We are committed to protecting the privacy of children.  In furtherance of this commitment, we restrict the use of our Website to persons eighteen (18) years of age or older.  We do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13).

**8\. Contact with You**

We may use your email address to contact you from time to time, in order to send notices required by law, to provide information regarding this Website, or to resolve any complaint.  We also reserve the right to call, mail, or email information to you about our services, to provide offers to customers, or to send out promotions to you.  You may at any time choose to unsubscribe (or “opt-out”) by contacting us at [info@grocerycouponhub.com](mailto:info@grocerycouponhub.com). Please type “UNSUBSCRIBE” in the subject line.  Also, we will include an unsubscribe link in each of our email messages, which shall never expire.   We will honor your unsubscribe request on or before the tenth (10th) day following our receipt of your request.  We will include our organization’s full postal mail address in every mail communication. 

**9\. Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy**

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time at our sole discretion and without prior notice.  If we make any material amendments, we will advise you about those changes by notifying you in a prominent place on our Website.  You should check back with us from time to time in order to confirm that there have been no significant changes.  
Please note that the use of information that we gather is subject to the Privacy Policy then in effect at the time of use. 

**10\. Third Parties**

On our Website you may be presented or directed to advertisements or promotional offers of third party advertisers. Such third party websites are moderated by third party companies and will not be subject to this privacy policy.  You should read any such privacy policy to confirm that you agree to its terms prior to participating with their websites or agreeing to complete any personal information requests.  If you wish to opt out of receiving mailings from third parties, you must do so directly with such third parties.

**11.  Other Legal Notices**

If you ever have a dispute over privacy or security, it will be subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.  We will always make every effort to resolve any concerns that you have regarding privacy that arises in connection with this Privacy Policy.

**12.  Other Information **

Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83, California residents who have provided or submitted personal information to us are permitted to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.  Within thirty (30) days of receiving such a request, we will provide a list of the categories of personal information disclosed to third parties for third party direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, along with the names and addresses of these third parties.  This request may not be made more than once per calendar year.  Further, in accordance with California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California residents are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with the California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R. Street, Ste. 1080, Sacramento, CA  95814 or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210 or by email to [dca@dca.ca.gov](mailto:dca@dca.ca.gov).  For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit [http://www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/).  

**13.  Complaints**

We accept privacy-related complaints to our Website via email and postal mail.

**14.  Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns over this Privacy Policy or if you need further information regarding the access to your personal information, or how your personal information is used, you may contact us as listed below:

GroceryCouponHub.com  
2885 Sanford Ave SW #16538  
Grandville, MI 49418

**15\. Effective Date**

This Privacy Policy was last modified on January 22, 2011.
